(Sheldon:)At least now
you can retrieve the black box...
...from the smoldering wreckage
that was once your fantasy of dating her...
...and analyze the data so that
you don't crash into geek mountain again.
(Howard:)I disagree. Love is not a sprint.
It's a marathon.
(Howard:)A relentless pursuit that only ends
when she falls into your arms...
(Howard:)...or hits you with the pepper spray.
No, I'm done with Penny.
I'm gonna be more realistic
and go after someone my own speed.
- Like who?
- I don't know.
(Leonard:)Olivia Geiger?
The dietitian at the cafeteria
with the limp and the lazy eye?
(Leonard:)- Yeah.
- Well, I don't think you have a shot there.
I have noticed that Leslie Winkle
recently started shaving her legs.
(Sheldon:)Now, given that winter is coming,
one can assume she's signaling...
(Sheldon:)...sexual availability.
(Leonard:)I don't know.
You guys work in the same lab.
- So?
- There are pitfalls.
(Howard:)Trust me, I know.
(Howard:)When it comes
to sexual-harassment law...